[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "Has commuting early become less of a problem? Have you ___ commute early?",
        "answer": "gotten used to"
    },
    {
        "question": "Maggie is a nurse. She is used to ___ at night.",
        "answer": "working"
    },
    {
        "question": "Her boyfriend is from Australia, so he isn’t used to ___ on the right side of a street.",
        "answer": "driving"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tom wasn’t so friendly in the past. He ___ be so friendly",
        "answer": "didn’t use to"
    },
    {
        "question": "The students were not used to ___ over an hour on their homework.",
        "answer": "spending"
    },
    {
        "question": "Her new working schedule is very demanding. She ___ it.",
        "answer": "isn’t used to"
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah has gotten used to ___ his dog out for a walk twice a day.",
        "answer": "taking"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you ___ play basketball in high school?",
        "answer": "use to"
    },
    {
        "question": "It’s taking her a long time to be used to ___ in a humid country.",
        "answer": "living"
    },
    {
        "question": "When I was a child, I used to ___ my sister’s clothes.",
        "answer": "wear"
    },
    {
        "question": "I ___ drinking a glass of warm milk before going to bed.",
        "answer": "am used to"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ella lived with her parents for a long time, but now she has her own apartment. She ___ live with her parents in the past.",
        "answer": "used to"
    },
    {
        "question": "They couldn’t recognize Ted because he didn’t use to ___ beard.",
        "answer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "We keep making mistakes on the new computer system. We need to ___ it as soon as possible.",
        "answer": "get used to"
    },
    {
        "question": "My uncle has moved to Madrid for six months and he still can’t get used to ___ lunch and dinner late .",
        "answer": "eating"
    },
    {
        "question": "I don’t usually have dinner early. I ___ having dinner early.",
        "answer": "am not used to"
    }
]